oh I gotta set the title I didn't do
[Music]
counter fact Oh regret memorization
mostly basic programming I know y'all
like basic programming
you're watching an app thank you I
really appreciate it when you guys watch
ads and subscribe I mean I do want to
make all my money from Instagram in the
future but at least for now you
subscribe to me on twitch is great but
make sure if you haven't already go
follow me uh after a child on Instagram
that's trying to set guy from Instagram
okay so we still have zero viewers I
don't know watch which isn't updating
but I see that we have people in the
chat so let's get started so
counterfactual regret minimize age you
have um so a lot of games that have been
solved in AI you take like checkers
chess go these are what's known as
perfect information games meaning they
all the state is visible there's no
there's no hidden state in the game and
all of those games are fairly Markovian
meaning you don't need to track lots of
state from previous so like the move
that someone took five moves ago if you
know the board stay its independent of
that move so it's a Markovian when you
take imperfect information games like
poker the actions that somebody takes
throughout the game gives you insight
into what their cards might be so we
have this algorithm called
counterfactual regret minimization
that's what everyone's using these days
I really don't know that much about it
um autosave failed
oh it's cuz I cleared my leave page
okay we need the toke and that's fine
cool so now we can say if this notebook
won't be working here in this notebook
there's an eye Python notebook yeah
right no we don't have people um I also
don't like that I can't see I can see
now yeah follow me on is Joe gallo go
seriously tell people follow me on
Instagram shelf my Instagram I want half
a million followers by the end of the
year and then that's all know I'm
Instagram famous okay regret magic
players reach equilibrium play by
tracking regrets for past place making
future plays proportional to positive
regret so you have this concept of
regret which is they talk about in
rock-paper-scissors means like look if
you play rock and your opponent played
paper you regret you regret playing rock
you regret not playing scissors you also
regret not playing pay you really regret
not playing scissors even more so they
have a worked example here usually it's
probably best to start at these examples
um so they talk a bit about Nash
equilibriums something that up on
Kapadia because if you don't get the
definition right it's kind of annoying
[Music]
each player is assumed game by chain
alone strategy so you guys know what the
Nash equilibrium is in
rock-paper-scissors
it's a mixed equilibrium meaning that in
order to play perfect
rock-paper-scissors you have to play
rock paper and scissors each with equal
probability because if you did it with a
different probability and you had like a
fixed strategy like here they even talk
about an opponent strategy which looks
like it plays Rock forty percent of the
time and paper and scissors 30% of the
time each that is not a good strategy
because the correct counter play
strategy that if you knew that was
exactly your opponent strategy
I think the correct counterplay strategy
would be always paper but that's also an
exploitable strategy thank you for
subscribing Lu Hart welcome to my
Twitter so that'd be it that'd be an
exploitable strategy so let's let's go
through this example regret matching
selects actions in proportion to
positive regrets of not having chosen in
the past copying all positive regrets
and some of them let's just stupidly
implement us get strategy so we have
this thing called normalizing some so
they use stupid C++ which is a really
bad choice I'm not sure I have to do
that I could also do NP double zeros
there I don't worry about that okay so
regret some strategy strategy some and
then the opponent strategy which looks
obviously like just probabilities of
I've acted right we don't you need those
stupid definitions but we know that
they're wrong paper and scissors
respective cool link to paper it's
called an introduction to counterfactual
regret minimization you could just
Google that I don't know it's all my
yeah there you go so I'm posted that Oh
excellent you posted the link to paper
you didn't ask cool thank you yeah good
someone give that guy a twitch cookie
okay I'm sorry let's look at what this
code isn't doing
okay so it looks like another way to
write this is just strategy equals NP
clip notice how this is actually the
same thing or actually really just NP
dah dah we want a maximum grab some zero
and then on the lighting some equals NP
dots on strategy
so I'm just copying this code rewriting
in Python gonna see we toast so coding a
Python 3 here so I can just do that and
[Music]
start right strategy right cool
all right see what this does he's gonna
get our strategy for our purposes so
because it was zero this stuff didn't
happen I really cool so get current
mixed strategy to regret matching so it
really just seems like we got rid of all
the negative regrets then normalized
that and if there wasn't any
normalization strategy we just assigned
them all equally which I could probably
write that a little bit cleaner ooh
face to the bottom-left it's on the
bottom left Oh is my face covering the
code you mean hold up here better I'll
move this down here then we'll increase
the chilling size more shilling for the
Instagram cool and I'll remember to not
use that that corner why no more of them
just two notebooks today I still use
them guess we're learning something
right I think the best way to learn is
called learn CFR it's my notebook over
here it's in a web browser
no it's Python 3 there's pretty nice
alright
mmm okay some readers might be idiots
and not know what an if statement is
normalizing some could be non-positive
such cases who make the Uniform probably
cumulated strategies I return Kevin so
strategy one could select an action
according to the probabilities yep
that's fine there's like a numpy thing
to do that I don't know
right now somebody could look it up
okay so okay alia get action so we'll
just write that there's a cuter way to
write this get action I think so get
action with respect to a strategy so I
think you just do like MP dot come some
strategy Shh numpy bisect here search
sorted yes this we do random random
random over here I know that's why my
faces and I'm not random is zero to one
uniform from zero to one I want
something they're just gonna do uniform
from zero to one which i think is yeah
return the next random floating-point
number they don't actually talk about
whether it's uniform why do you need to
solve imperfect info game as well isn't
the world an imperfect information game
not make an Instagram box guys we're
gonna fill those legitimate real social
following by the way if anyone hope that
works for Facebook you know I'd love if
you could get me verified give you my
bro will go out to the club together
let's try it
MP dot search sorted and because I'm
strategy should be this so this is
strategy so I'm actually increasing it
is okay whatever
yeah so if we do get action to zero zero
let's just let's just test this quickly
Ryan range 100 equals
say equals this hundred just just like
let's like do a sanity check and do like
lots were today okay cool so it's about
130 each which is right there now if
you're playing against at opponent yet
charge I don't know what the charge is
I'll go do that but what I could do that
right now okay cool that's about that's
about random right actually gonna play
was on cool let's just see like with the
variances is kind of your variance it's
kind of cute right
don't we love plot had plots sorted this
guy taught me this and I was like man
that's a good trick for if you don't
remember what PLT dot hist you know
that I get cool with the building blocks
in place we can now construct our
training algorithm
I do kind of like my one-liner look I
can put random dot random there though
that may still be a one-liner oh how
nice would that be uh make money selling
ups I know yo no mention in that
all right where were we train get the
grip matched mixed strategy actions
compute action utilities accumulate
action regrets okay well that sounds
easy enough
[Music]
follow me mr. Graham guys forgiven
number of iterations okay so remember
our opponent is gonna play rock 40% of
the time so I think the strategy should
converge to always pape well we did
always paper if we played always paper
against the strategy we'd have a 30% tie
rate of 30 percent loss rate and a 40
percent win rate which i think is the
best you can do
okay we're writing a Rock Paper
Scissors bot I think you can follow this
but please follow me on instagram
compute the utility
let's just let's just write a quick
funky called value so if zero is rock
now let's just write that this isn't
this isn't genius we're writing a
rock-paper-scissors bot
don't be noobs now thank you thank you
please promote my Instagram if you want
me to do more streams it's not even
about subscribing a twitch anymore I do
really appreciate the subscriptions but
I appreciate more increasing my
Instagram followers my goal is to have a
million by the end of the year okay so
if value from the perspective of P 1 P 2
if P 1 equals equals wrong and P 2 okay
so first off P 1 equals equals T 2
retiring 0 because there's no value for
player 1 that's a tie if player 1 played
raw and play or 2 played scissors we
know scissors smashes rock there's
probably like a smart way to just like
use the fact these the numbers I gave it
no no a million Instagram how would i
monetize Instagram followers I don't
know yet but really guys it's about you
know we're not gonna go into that right
now okay player 1 plays scissors and I
caught paper and paper covers rock
there's some ways to do this is like
mods and but like do you want to
think about that right now I know I
don't cool um so let's just do this
let's play 100 rounds of let's play
thousand rounds of rock-paper-scissors
don't be cheap and then let's see what
my value is 41 28 31 negative 23 this
probably isn't enough to get a real
sampling oh let's play 100 rounds of 10
and also this is a noob it's
probably a magical way to do this with
like range estimators and stuff they
talk about this stuff on the paper but
you know I'm an idiot so
I think I don't know maybe fit a
Gaussian to that let's I mean that's
pretty small so I don't think we're
exploiting at all
yeah so after playing all those games of
rock-paper-scissors yeah we're not we're
not exploiting at all but just let's uh
let's try for a sec let's try that
strategy that I was talking about and
see what value we can get so that
strategy would be always paper so never
rock always pay for a never scissors
[Music]
no cheetah yes that doesn't matter
actually you really shouldn't do this I
always run into problems like NP copy
okay look now we're getting an average
value of 10 see this value of 10 so
we're exploiting him by always playing
paper that's right um please follow me
on instagram if you haven't really
follow me in Instagram you know I love
Instagram power cycle okay now of course
I hand coded that strategy so let's see
if we can use counterfactual regret
minimization to learn that strategy
because we want to do machine learning
this is a machine learning channel for
those who just followed we're coding
rock paper scissors agents um so my
opponent is pretty stupid plays rock 40%
of the time paper 30% of time and
scissors 30% of time so it seems like we
can get 10 value out of him 10 out of
100 so we're getting we're getting 10 I
don't know this is like proper way to
talk about this but let me tell you why
I'm interested in this stuff I know you
guys like the rants there's money in
imperfect information games there's no
money as perfect information gives in
here's why when you play chess against
somebody it's quick to tell who's who's
good at chess and who's bad at chess
right you're not gonna you're not gonna
play somebody against chess for money
but my chassis laws like 1400 all right
if you have a lower low if you have like
a you know thousand T low I'm gonna beat
you if you have an 1800 eat long you're
gonna be me there's no reason that we
need to wager on this but with imperfect
information games there's much more
variance and it's much easier for people
to wrongly estimate how good they are
with respect to somebody else so if we
learn how to play imperfect information
games we can make money and then with
money we can buy expensive like
Gucci and Fendi and Prada and and
javante and and the you know st. Laurent
all those rich people brands and then we
can post that on my Instagram so I
become Instagram famous I'm satisfied
with you but you know really what we got
to do is convert you guys into an
Instagram audience that will go with
that you got to take high quality photos
I know I know I know
look look we're looking into that we're
looking into that you don't want we're
gonna get money we're gonna pay a guy
he's gonna be my Instagram guy and he's
gonna be a millions of followers okay oh
you missed the old rants I know you
missed the aldryn that was a different
there was a different character that was
George Hotz the common I see you and I
work in research and I do this all
day I'm very satisfied with my twitchy's
oh no guys it's a weird year it's 2019
its sanity 2019 everything's changing
you got to keep up with the times be
left behind okay
golden keyboard
[Music]
where is action utilities initial oh
it's initialized okay all right so let's
just write whoops what did that do
it's not that long just try to write
this training iterations
[Music]
no no guys we're not living in the past
you know we're not talking about how
like this was done manner this was done
that this is the future we're gonna live
in the future
futures crazy place it's just I'm just
cleaning a colorful bit okay ah we want
to say action utility oh yeah can I just
do that that's the same thing as
actually doing the the tuple with one
right so that's equivalent to that yes
it is oh cool
get rid of characters save characters
save typing time be faster next time
coding I know they're shorter you can
write your code number code is written
you write code in order to be read not
to be yeah I know I know
now what programming today I mean
sometimes I just come on the stream
because you guys are like I like talking
out loud and when I talk to myself I
just seem weird but when I talk to I'm
talking to 200 people right now it's
like a lecture Broce the future really
is a crazy place it's Merritt it's hard
to do things watching yourself and
marina
um no no I'm the files are kind of
over you can see you can check my github
I implemented a lot of I just want to
like a number theory textbook
maybe they implemented like 20 proofs
from it it's good tools aren't really
good enough yet and I mean it's a
company idea right like you could take a
company you can make you could make good
tools for that kind of programming I
mean a really cool thing about that kind
of programming is you can't write bugs
but even with the amount of bugs I write
in Python I'm still more productive in
Python than it would be in a language
like train
[Music]
I don't really understand this okay
other action equals 2 then 0 gassy just
like wrap it round see that you see what
they're doing there it's like wrap
around I'll just copy is fine
basically if it's to the next one zero
and I guess this is for for
[Music]
rock-paper-scissors
I don't just copy the normal thing to do
it more
no comedy knees are ultra rare exclusive
March you could have bought them at one
point but you know what they say get an
early get rich getting late get
cumulate action we're grads alright so
we're back to this idea of regrets some
actually isn't it is used here well it's
a strategy okay it's a strategy if I
have a strategy okay so my regret equals
[Music]
the action utility minus the action
utility of my action got some plus
equals notice how they're doing this all
with four loops so you don't really have
to do four loops thank you thank you 24
new followers and it's to keep the
followers coming guys this is a follower
shell stream I love you all if you can
get me followers because we need
followers them we need to be in coma
Instagram lover how does dream like two
weeks ago I was lying in bed it was this
girl it smoked a bit of weed and I was
just like ranting for an hour about how
I'm gonna be an Instagram celebrity and
then never hear the secret you know it's
like that when you like say
something it becomes true what am i
starting a new company yeah that's a
great question right um you say some a
lot of times and it becomes true well
that's how I felt with this look every
scams are over guys scams are over the
best thing is just be authentic and be
real
they're not gonna copyright me for this
oh man that is a great song if you guys
haven't heard it
[Music]
if I turn what if they're right
what if I ruin Broadway by being in this
ad tonight I see what you're saying
and I make you this pact I will never
make again so long
[Music]
that way the rainbow taste the rainbow
here the full cast recording one Spotify
Michael last week you expressed some
anxiety about storing in skittles
commercial the Broadway musical yes I
have been having some doubts I mean I
don't really do ads well it wouldn't be
stressful to be seen by millions of
people in the big game no just to be
clear the ad won't be on the actual game
people will buy takes much longer but no
there's a whole album it's called
skittles advertising the musical um it
really is great no I wasn't getting the
pie I was taking a piss real okay
for each individual iteration we're
training our regrets may be temporarily
skewed in such way an influencer
strategy is a- regrets um you know
chosen converges to a minimal regret
strategy is the average strategy across
all iterations is this it
I think I can use value here
and then yeah okay there was the action
energy you see you brethren thank you
for watching ten Prince
this is actually a really stupid way to
write this okay see you see what it's
doing right like it's kind of annoying
this is a stupid alright this I can just
say other action plus 1 mod num actions
these guys are noobs and I want to
confirm that mod and pythons way to like
minus 1 mod gnome actions goats - I
understand they even wrote a paragraph
introducing inline if statements like I
know the guy like discovered in line of
statements and you know I get excited
now there's the thing about these kind
of research people like some of them are
absolute geniuses and I understand math
I never will but then they like code and
they came Oh strategy some plus equals
strategy
small right
that's just not right
how did strategy some become three what
oh okay
so here are my regrets I regret playing
rock not at all cuz I don't understand
why that's negative that's weird
cumulate action regrets
I mean looks like we're close I just
need to write this last function yet
average strategy so what we're expecting
to get and we can run it down here once
we have a strategy is a value of about
when I delete that I think the optimal
strategy against a agent we should use
the right word for this an agent with a
stationary distribution that favors
wrong is to always play paper so that
strategy is that when you encode it in
strategy for him and this gives me a
mean value of 10 so I think that's the
best we can do so that's what we're
hoping for when we run this at the end
you know it's always nice to write your
evaluator
to my misspelled average okay equals NP
zeroes please uh follow me on Instagram
you know just that's my real dream in
life okay wait this looks like denticles
to get strategy
great it's just identical to get
strategy I think normalizing sums just a
sum the normal sum is greater than zero
sure oh well they're not doing this zero
thing it just doesn't make sense I don't
really understand what this does but I
think that it's just that if I take that
line away negative regrets up well that
sounds are highly okay yeah this this is
computer in a manner similar to get
strategy without the need to be
concerned negative values okay I mean
again I don't really understand that but
okay so let's train for a lot of ethics
and then
okay so strategy is global thing that I
don't really have anywhere Oh
so this is strategy some we don't have
that at all strategy I don't even
understand like I don't know what this
is used for period because it's used
here like like that used to be a global
variable let's just make sure sometimes
you restart your notebooks make sure you
don't have just a little bit hanging
around that you're using
[Music]
oh no strategy just come to Uncle I can
treat you today okay so this key what's
not working in that one strategy some
use strategy some I don't know it's
basic okay let's get the average
strategy and see what we have local
variable strategy reference before her
oh my god I hate when stupid numpy does
this put this up in here I just have one
block that I copy set print options per
se it's true
okay now it looks correct I think the
strategy is exactly right so almost
never play Rock almost always play paper
and almost ever play scissors so if we
just replace this with strategy equals
get averaged strategy there we go ten
point two okay we just learned the
perfect strategy you think this is basic
do you understand this algorithm do you
honestly can you honestly tell me you
understand what this what this algorithm
is I don't know just kind of copied you
from this now let's see if we can
try to understand it okay so like this
is poorly written because the others
accumulates like this shouldn't be here
they should pass in regrets um let's
refactor this
move these down into train
this is better way to code because you
want to stick you wanna stick Global's
everywhere global some pretty nasty
especially in articles you write too
it's also doesn't eject me gnome actions
I could just say a strategy that shapes
of the CRL there's also ones like closer
to the same thing
is that really small right like it
doesn't look spelled right strat eg I
guess it is right
I mean asked repeatedly what's your
problem
I don't know op time come in all that
is
that's right I don't even know what
average strategy was it's just a stupid
thing they used in there it's fine so
they really are you see much simpler
that is like once you write things that
aren't terrible you shouldn't do that
you see the danger there so let's just
learn em get our coffee in there start
let's see if it all runs no mansions is
not defined well stupid race condition
alright alright then of course we train
it for more don't the verge better how
am I gonna draw that little plot as well
get strategy requires one positional
argument strategy cool so it always
picks paper it's a paper his action one
I am so rock paper scissors paper Swan
this isn't in blue which starts that one
all hey Lu Italy okay guys I think we
learned about counterfactual
urbanization neither I will stream in
our let's go through and make sure we
actually understand what's codes doing
okay
so qu
late current strategy based on regrets
[Music]
select my and Poland's
action
okay let's so I mean this is the rules
of rock-paper-scissors here the action
utility of the other action so if we
yeah you always want to do the next one
so we can say like if P plus one loss
that's covered by so we want to do this
MA remember how I said we could do is
cute thing with a mod equals p2 so paper
we want if player two pays paper we want
to play the previous action which is
rock so that'll clean up that code now
if we were doing this in Cocke you know
be kind of beautiful because we could
confirm those two things are equivalent
like I wish it was just a way to just do
that in Python right leg over the same
function we just say those two functions
are equivalent
[Music]
eight that's pathetic why do you do so
badly call variance guys even if you're
you know playing an advantage you can
still lose here's gotta remember that
how they coded in Java
okay the average strategies computer
regret matching in other words is this
the best respond to their strategy you
might not be obvious because always a
pure it might not be obvious but there's
always a pure best response strategy to
any mix strategy I mean I guess alright
cuz even if you have the correct mixed
strategy of rock-paper-scissors which is
one-third one-third one-third I can play
I can play always Rock and it'll do the
same there's no agent that'll play
against that better the only difference
is exploitability they go into this
stuff called local best response Oh
modified so both players use your grant
matching should we do that you actually
write that eight is just like my number
out of a hundred my my wins some winning
what I say that in poker I'd be like
yeah it means my advantage is like if we
play for a hundred I expect a dollar
each I expect if we play a hundred times
for a dollar each I expect to be up ten
dollars which I'm sure there's an
explicit way to calculate it but I don't
know it
a median a better estimator of the chef
oh yeah 10-point know exactly oh yeah
look at that median estimator solid all
right let's do it
okay so if we're gonna train both our
players with 2p iterations just all
right this tumbly well we can write it a
little bit smarter
all right
she'd be perfectly symmetric hey I do
suck a chance I we got five minutes to
do this let's go let's go let's go let's
go by the way guys this is really just
for me to shield free Instagram
followers so please go on Instagram
right now tell your friends tell your
mother
tell your sister tell your dogs and dogs
have Instagram accounts to go follow
after our trials on Instagram that's
right thank you rs poni for subscribing
I appreciate every subscriber just being
assigned to every time so this can
actually go inside the loop
okay so put this down here move these
two new thingy entertain that's no it's
not exactly gonna work that's okay
actually you know regrets um here and
strategy some here
I also have to pass in my opponent
strategy again you see up
whenever you use global variables
don't use global variables burrows and
return the two things we update look at
this functional programming ish
it still works I know it could pass in
the opponent strategy every day from
here
starts I'm not I'm dangling Global's
global variables are a bad choice if
you're using global variables you made
bad choices good news is you can fix
your bad choices by refactoring be a bro
refactor and don't use global variables
because somebody someday is gonna be
reading your code and I'm gonna be like
why is only global variables all
right so now we want to go to player
let's say regrets on p1 walls s do we
actually need to track both of these I
think we do yes we do
got some p2 a song p1 strategy some T
two generations
all right let's train player one now
what school is for opponent strategy we
say equals get average strategy get
average strategy this is why I like
using them get over strategies judges so
this is train p1
and we should know what this converges
to it should be because they're both
trying to exploit each other it should
be just 1/3 1/3 1/3 for both of them
[Music]
turned strategy some p1
no it's not ready to get a machete yeah
sure just the same as calling normalizer
like that's all it does yeah it just
calls him harm home has is so stupid
okay well that isn't what it converged
to but it really may not matter there
might be no things forcing this to
converge to anything
[Music]
yeah as garrotted s
as long as this is zero I think it's
just right wait 30 not as up yeah
okay this is not an okay strategy all
right let's figure out what happened two
players are some game pair of average
strategies converges to a neat Nash
equilibrium okay maybe this is like
unstable like Ganz you know so hope to
try something like this where they like
train against each other for a bet or
did I just make a typo I think we might
have to reset the over gret some here
try resetting them both I don't know
I'll try just resetting one and see what
happens
do anymore
and keep your rats local yeah that's
closer more Oh run run run run yeah okay
so that's much better
now when we run them against each other
we're still getting that because I
didn't run this okay cool
so that's very close to zero okay so it
works let's see if we can take this
outside and if it still works or do you
have to do the regret sums I know what
we did the first time didn't work train
train train train train no see that
doesn't work okay so you have to reset
the regret sums every time or it doesn't
work as for why that's true
maybe we'll leave that as an exercise to
the reader because I don't know but it
certainly seems true now if you want it
to converge to this stuff yeah no I mean
okay you can kind of see why right if
the other opponent is playing a strategy
where they're always playing Rock right
you're gonna say oh well my strategy is
I'm always gonna play paper and you're
gonna you're gonna really regret every
time you don't play paper um but then
your opponents like oh hey wait a second
this guy's moron he's always playing
paper imma always play scissors so um
you know what I have an idea let's uh
this isn't that many iterations
let's put strategy every time
yeah okay cool you see what Convergys so
yeah look she can see the first one here
player 1 had a propensity toward rock
player 2 learned always uh always play
paper then yeah yeah well I was really
cool player 2 Oh this worked way better
than I thought I look I love when things
work so this thing learned to have a
propensity towards scissors for some
reason despite that it well I guess it's
just a small propensity some reason I
learned to never play scissors oh I
guess cuz that was okay that was the
strategy from before where it never
played scissors then it learns that it
has to start playing scissors again then
it plays this which isn't really
exploitable cool I mean I wonder if we
could put it to K factor on the strategy
or even if we have to we probably don't
that's probably one of the cool things
about it well you see that it eventually
converges I wonder if we can even lower
this number is this number you can see
yeah yeah needs a few more than that
didn't say this algorithm was fast guys
cool yeah it's converging and like
that's close to an equilibrium but you
know things take a long time so really
cool look you wanted to play early rock
I don't know why he learns early rock
maybe you might using the same random
seeds or something but uh yeah and
there's probably 27 subtle bugs in this
that's making it less than perfect I'm
pretty happy with that we built an
automatic rock-paper-scissors a I pull
like the stream give me your feedback
and also don't forget follow me on
Instagram
she's over there now so look that's I
gotta use the other hand so it's over
there so that I see the see the
Instagram hope you all enjoyed there's
some high quality programming content
the algorithms called counterfactual
regret minimization and it is the key to
solving high complexity imperfect
information games oh why don't we go
what are we gonna play the knows
about that our PS game thank you thank
you for following on Instagram tell
everybody you know I want a million
followers by the end of the year I
believe in you guys I don't know I don't
know how I'm gonna do it yet but never
just believe man you ever know them of
them am i sharing that too bitter nope
nope no it's a secret
oh I got all bloated somewhat about
effort you can even retype it you learn
stuff by doing it thank you thank you
Pokhara alright what's up by twitches
bye see you later from beautiful lovely
LA with my got some candles I got some
other thing behind me no vinton a we did
ipython notebooks high quality ahh
bye bye bye bye